express-press-release.net 2017-07-26

# Express Press Release Distribution (Free) - Privacy Policy

Home \- Privacy Policy 

**EPR Network's Privacy Policy**

[EPR Network](http://epr-network.com/) respects your concerns about the privacy. At the same time, we do ask and collect information about you in order for us to understand your needs better and make your experience at EPR Network more valuable to you. We created this Privacy Policy to give you with notice of what information EPR Network may collect, how such information may be used or shared with third parties, and how such information relates to the operation of the Site. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms of Service (the "TOS") posted on the Site, including the provisions regarding change or modification of this Privacy Policy and other policies as set forth in the TOS. You are responsible for checking this page periodically for changes and updates to the Privacy Policy. Your use of the Site following any posted changes to the Privacy Policy will be deemed an acceptance of such changes. This Privacy Policy is part of, and incorporated into, the TOS. 

The EPR Network is not intended for use by persons under the age of thirteen. Individuals who are under the age of thirteen are expressly prohibited from submitting to EPR Network or posting to the Site any personally identifiable information about themselves. 

By providing any personal information to this Site, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in the United States and/or any other country. 

This Privacy Policy explains: 

  * what personally identifiable information EPR Network collects from you, and how EPR Network uses the information;
  * with whom your information may be shared;
  * what choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information;
  * what cookies are, and how EPR Network uses them; 
  * how EPR Network protects your personal information;
  * how you can access, update or delete your information;
  * what else you should know about your online privacy; 

(i) What personally identifiable information EPR Network collects from you, and how EPR Network uses the information.

EPR Network collects and stores personal information in several ways at different parts of our Site. This information may include your legal name, email address, age, gender, address, telephone number(s), areas of interest, financial information, User ID, User Password and other self-identifying information. We collect this information in order to provide you with our services more easily, and in a more personalized manner. We may make message boards and discussion forums available to you. If you choose to voluntarily disclose certain information on any such public area of the Site, this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. We urge exercising caution when disclosing information on public message boards or discussion forums. 

EPR Network also may request certain information using online order forms for products and services. On the order forms, we may collect contact information, financial information, demographic information, method of payment and, if applicable, a credit or debit card number. We may also collect information about you in surveys or for sweepstakes and contests on the Site and information about the searches you perform and the pages you visit on the Site. EPR Network may also monitor, on an anonymous aggregate basis, patterns of use in connection with emails that it sends out, including which links are clicked on in our email communications, so that we may use such information to better personalize the content of the Site and our mailings for our users. All such information will be protected in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We may also automatically collect your Internet Protocol address to help diagnose problems and for system administration. EPR Network reserves the right to request any additional information necessary to establish and maintain your account for use of the Site.

EPR Network uses the information collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Information we collect is used to customize your experience at our Site. We also show you content that we think will be interesting to you, and display content according to the preferences you indicate while on our Site. EPR Network may use your information to send you promotional materials about EPR Network and its partners. We may also use your information to contact you, if necessary. 

(ii) With whom your information may be shared.

EPR Network will not sell, rent or barter your personal information other than to its business partners as set forth herein. However, we may from time to time aggregate statistical information regarding our customers, traffic patterns and site usage, or sell our research, which may contain aggregate information. In addition, we may report aggregate information to our advertisers. Such aggregate information will not individually identify any user.

In order to provide you with co-branded services, and to improve our features, we will sometimes share your information with our partners. 

We reserve the right to disclose any information if such action is necessary (a) to conform to the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process or subpoena served on EPR Network, (b) to protect and defend the legal rights or property of EPR Network, the Site, or its users, or (c) in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of its users or the general public. We further reserve the right to release any information concerning any user if that user participates (or is reasonably suspected of participating) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution. 

It is possible that EPR Network, its subsidiaries, its joint ventures, or any combination of such, could merge with or be acquired by another business entity. Should such a combination occur, you should expect that EPR Network would share some or all of your information in order to continue to provide the service. Notice of any such event (to the extent it occurs) will be posted on the EPR Network website, and we will require that the new combined entity follow the practices disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

(iii) What choices you have regarding the collection, use and distribution of your information.

You may occasionally receive information about the products or services you have selected to place on your personal EPR Network pages, which may include EPR Network products and services, and the products and services of our partners. EPR Network believes that these updates are interesting and informative. In the event you are requested to register, you may be given an opportunity to "opt in" to receive mailings from EPR Network and/or its partners by "checking" a box in the registration form. If you submit a registration form with the box checked, you thereby consent to being placed on this mailing list. You may subsequently contact us to request to be removed from this list. In every update that we send, we may include an option to discontinue receipt of future updates. EPR Network reserves the right to limit any registrations on our Site to those who will accept our information and to those who will provide the requested information. 

(iv) What cookies are, and how EPR Network uses them. 

As part of press releaseing and providing customizable and personalized services, EPR Network may sometimes use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. All portions of the Site that prompt you to log in or that are customizable require that you accept cookies. No other company has access to cookies placed on your computer by EPR Network unless you select the option, upon registering with the Site, to share user-information with EPR Network's partners. We may use cookies technology to reduce the time required for you to submit your requests and for EPR Network to respond to such requests. Cookies will not be used by us to retrieve any information about you, or from your computer, that you have not voluntarily given to us. Cookies may also be placed on your computer when you link from the Site to our partners' web sites or when you click banner ads provided on our Site. Cookies placed on your computer by third parties by or through the Site, if any, are not the responsibility of EPR Network and are not subject to the TOS. Please contact the third party placing these cookies to find out what information is collected and how it is used. You can usually edit your browser not to accept cookies, but the features of our Site may not function properly if you do not accept cookies.

UPDATE AS OF JULY 2015

More particularly, we use the following third-party sites, services and features that use cookies to personalize content and ads (Google AdSense and DoubleClick), to provide social media features (Facebook, Twitter and Google+) and to analyze our traffic (Google Analytics and Quantcast). We also share information about your use of our site with those social media, advertising and analytics partners. While we have no control over their use of the data, we do believe this use does not pose any threat to you.

If you would like to change your browser's preferences you may do so by following the instructions [here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1).

You can learn more about how Google uses data when you use their services on EPR Network's sites [over here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

The following pages are the policies that govern and provide more information about the use of the data when you use the services of those companies on EPR Network's sites.

  * Facebook Privacy Policy - <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>;
  * Google Privacy Policy - <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>;
  * Google Analytics' Privacy Policy - <http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>;
  * Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on - <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>;
  * Quantcast Privacy Policy - <https://www.quantcast.com/privacy/>;
  * Twitter Privacy Policy - <https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en>;

END OF UPDATE 

(v) How EPR Network protects your personal information.

For all our transactions, we employ reasonable and current Internet security methods and technologies. Where appropriate, we password protect, use encryption techniques and install firewalls. We strive to protect you. We encourage our participating service providers to adopt and honor their own consumer privacy policies. For all our efforts to safeguard your privacy, no system can be guaranteed. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, or that we transmit to you, or guarantee that it will be free from unauthorized access by third parties. Once we receive your information, we use reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. 

(vi) How you can access, update or delete your information.

There is no option for updating your information on previously posted press releases. This is our philosophy to act as public archive for press releases and opportunities and you only could submit new press release but not to modify an existing one.

(vii) What else you should know about your online privacy.

The Site may also contain links to other web sites and advertising. The privacy policies of those web sites and advertisers may significantly differ from that of our Site. It is your responsibility to contact such web site operator or advertiser directly to determine their privacy policy. 

Should you have more questions don’t hesitate to contact us at info [at] epr-network.com. Additionally you may wish to get familiar with our terms of service before using EPR Network. 

(effective as of July 01, 2004, revised on December 2006, June 2008, last revision July 2015)
